Marzet Khatit

Frontend Developer

I am a frontend developer with a strong background of over five years in IT support and a Bachelor's degree in Information Systems and Technology. My professional experience includes technical support, problem solving and web development.

I am currently working as frontend developer with our international team.

https://www.linkedin.com/in/marzet

https://t.me/stairwayto hell

https://stairwaytohell.github.io – portfolio

Work experience

Frontend developer

Self-employment, Krasnodar, RU (from 11/2020 to Present)

Technical Support Specialist

Service-partner, Krasnodar, RU (from 11/2018 to 02/2021 – 2 years 2 months)

Webmaster

Freelance, Krasnodar, RU (from 06/2015 to 10/2018 – 3 years 10 months)

Technical Support Specialist

Transcard System, Krasnodar, RU (06/2016 to 03/2018 – 1 year 10 months)

Intern

Kuban State University, Krasnodar, RU (12/2014 to 07/2015 – 8 months)

Technical Support Specialist

Rostelecom, Krasnodar, RU (10/2013 to 12/2014 – 1 year 3 months)

Education

Kuban State University (2010 to 2015) Bachelor's degree Information Systems and Technology

Skills

JavaScript, HTML/CSS

Certifications

Responsive Web Design freeCodeCamp https://www.freecodecamp.org/certification/stairwayto_hell/responsive-web-design

Languages

Russian (Bilingual proficiency)
Adyghe (Bilingual proficiency)
English (Professional working proficiency)